http://www.schweitzer.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Schweitzer Mountain ResortPrivacy Statement and DisclosuresInformation Collection & Use Schweitzer Mountain Resort collects personally identifiable information from a variety of sources including:Hotel RegistrationsWebsite RegistrationsSeason Pass SalesSki School RegistrationsCustomer Loyalty Program Data provided by our business partnersVarious Contests, Promotions and GiveawaysSchweitzer Mountain Resort is also the sole owner of the following website domain names and all data collected through them:www.schweitzer.comProducts and ServicesIf you purchase a product or service online from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our login and checkout pages. These products and services include but are not limited to products from www.schweitzer.com. You must provide contact information (such as name, e-mail, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.Upon furnishing your personally identifiable information, Schweitzer Mountain Resort will enter that information into our corporate marketing database. You will begin to receive periodic e-mail and direct mail communications, which include e-newsletters, surveys and special promotions.Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. To be removed from our direct mail database, please e-mail messenger@schweitzer.com or submit your request in writing to:Schweitzer Mountain Resort Marketing Department10000 Schweitzer Mountain RoadSandpoint, ID83864Web site www.schweitzer.comSocial Security NumbersSocial Security Numbers are not collected from our customers or used for any purpose.Surveys or ContestsFrom time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).Your personally identifiable information will be added to our corporate marketing database and used as described under the "Products and Services" section above.Your customer survey ratings will be used as a tool to help us improve our products and services.Special Offers and UpdatesWe will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions through the use of monthly e-newsletters and individual email campaigns.ProfilesWe do not collect profile information through the use of cookies or log files.  Schweitzer Mountain Resort will share profile information with other third parties that have contracted with us in new business ventures.Supplementation of InformationIn order to keep your contact information current, we use a third party to verify your postal address prior to any direct mailing. Your records will also be checked for a change-of-address form filed at the United States Post Office. Our corporate marketing database will be updated as a result of this process.Information Sharing and DisclosurePersonally Identifiable InformationWe Occasionally Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.In the normal course of business, Schweitzer Mountain Resort will contract with certain business partners to develop new product or service offerings. As a normal part of these business ventures, our corporate marketing database will be shared with our business partner.AgentsWe use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.Service ProvidersSchweitzer Mountain Resort does not utilize any third party service providers at this time.Legal DisclaimerWe reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web sites.Choice/Opt-outIf you no longer wish to receive our e-newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions (update profile/unsubscribe link) included at the bottom of each e-newsletter or email communication. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications by contacting us at messenger@schweitzer.com or by mail (See the "Contact Us" section) to opt-out.Announcements of any third parties planning on using your personal information will be made on our corporate Web site at www.schweitzer.com, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.Log FilesAs is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track user movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information.We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses a small JavaScript string on each web page to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate state of what information is captured, e.g., usage and volume statistics to assist in analyzing our Web site traffic trends and patterns.CookiesWe may use cookies from time to time to help you, for example, to navigate efficiently between secure and non-secure pages of our site; to participate in sweepstakes or monthly drawings; or to help us identify special interests that you may have and that enhance your experience on our websites. "Cookies" are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use all of the features of our site, including purchasing tickets and other products online. We may track the website you come from or go to. We may track what browser you use so as to send you pages appropriate for your browser. We may also collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. We may use this information for the operation of online services, to maintain quality of online services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of this website.The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.Tracking TagsWe use tracking tags such as pixels or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partners including DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and tracking tag technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/.Links to Other SitesVarious links across Schweitzer's web site do contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Schweitzer. Please be aware that we, Schweitzer Mountain Resort, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Schweitzer Mountain Resort.Access to Personally Identifiable InformationIf your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.SecurityThe security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or shopping pages, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link.We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at messenger@schweitzer.com.Business TransitionsIn the event Schweitzer Mountain Resort goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via e-mail or notice on our corporate Web site schweitzer.com of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.Changes in this Privacy StatementIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page at schweitzer.comContact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:Schweitzer Mountain Resort 10000 Schweitzer Mountain RoadSandpoint, ID83864www.schweitzer.com
